https://immedica.com/privacy-policy/

Immedica Pharma privacy policyGDPR – General Data Protection Regulation effective from May 25, 2018This privacy policy sets out how Immedica Pharma AB and its affiliates (Immedica) uses and protects any information that you give Immedica when you use this website or email Immedica.Immedica is committed to ensure that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, it will only be used in accordance with this privacy policy.Immedica may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. This policy is effective from May 25, 2018
What we collectWe may collect the following information from emails sent to us:Name and job title, affiliationContact information including email addressWhen reporting adverse events or complaints we record an identifiable reporter, an identifiable patient with gender, age, age group or initials.What we do with the information we gatherWe save this information to answer your email and for the following reasons:Internal record keeping of email conversations/questions regarding our pharmaceutical productsWhen receiving complaints or reports of adverse events where we are obligated by law to keep records and forward the information to authorities/partner companiesWe may periodically send information to health care professionals regarding disease awareness or information regarding changes of product package sizes, formulation or reimbursement for approved products. SecurityWe are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. To prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.Controlling your personal informationWe will not sell or lease your personal information to third parties unless we are required by law to do so.You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998 or GDPR.If you believe that any information, we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to Immedica Pharma AB, Norrtullsgatan 15, 113 29 Stockholm or email us as soon as possible at privacy@immedica.com. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.Links to other websitesOur website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.Stockholm May 2018
CONTACT
Privacy policy | Term of Use | Code of ConductImmedica Pharma ABNorrtullsgatan 15113 29 StockholmSwedenE-mail: info@immedica.comPhone: +46(0)8 533 39 500© 2019
All rights Reserved. Design by Immedica
Linkedin
Headquarter
Local medical information
Ordering
Safety and product complaints
Partnering request
